Contact

wuse II, Abuja, Nigeria +234913103909 (Mobile) dicethedev@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/blessing-samuel-6a72b1211 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

JavaScript Vue.js PHP

Languages

English (Professional Working)

Honors-Awards

Most Sociable Student of the Year

Blessing Samuel

Software Engineer intern @printriteng --- JavaScript, Vuejs, PHP & Nodejs. Blessing is always learning and ready to learn from you. #NFT fans #DiceverseNFT is coming soon Abuja

Summary

Blessing Samuel is a technical expert in the areas of software engineering, using the programming

languages C++, JavaScript, Vuejs, PHP, Nodejs, MySQL, MongoDB. Blessing love programming and designing things that live on the internet. My interest is web development and my web development journey started back then in 2019 when I decided to try to work on a free HTML template. I am very

adept using JavaScript and its frameworks like Vue, Angular. I can work with zeal and real wizardy.

Blessing does not love talking about himself in the 3rd person. He want to learn New things, because that's what brings joy to his life Up. He believe in team success & growth, however he always put his best & maintain a strong team bonding for every project he get to work on. Here are a few technologies I've been working with recently: JavaScipt, Vue, MYSQI, PHP & Nodejs.

Experience

Printrite NG

11 months

Frontend Engineer
July 2021 - Present (9 months)
Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria

- Work with languagues, platforms, frameworks, and content management systems such as PHP, VueJs, Nodejs, Github, Bitbucket, JavaScript, SQL and Figma.
- Tested sites in various browsers and devices to ensure cross-browser compatibility and mobile responsiveness.
- Communicate with integrative teams of developers/engineers, designers and clients.

User Interface Designer

May 2021 - July 2021 (3 months)

Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria

I use FIGMA software for UI/UX Design

Excel at:

- Designing layouts, producing images, and developing styles for Websites, Mobile Design App.
- Interfaced with user experience designers and other developers to ensure thoughtful and reasonable user experiences across myShelta.com Web app.
- Contributing creative ideas during corporate brainstorming sessions.
- Getting a lot with team members and also contributing ideas.

Dicemedia Studio
Graphic Designer
August 2019 - Present (2 years 8 months)
Abuja, Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria

I'm the Co-founder of Dicemedia Studio. I started my Graphic Designing journey back in 2019 down till date. I'm well experienced with over 2 years experience and i can handle any graphic design jobs i have opportunity to get on to work with. Help a lot of brand on their graphic design products. I'm a team builder, working with teams has been my priority.

You can locate dicemedia studio official handle on Instagram for more information.

Education

Nigeria Korea Friendship Institute of Vocational & Advanced Technology

National Innovation Diploma, Computer Software Engineering · (2020 - 2022)

Onward Comprehensive Academy

High School Diploma · (2015 - 2019)